Windows 10 is about to release a massive new build that cannot be held off
and they are doing something very risky and dangerous; they are merging 
Microsoft Edge, and the file explorer, and even with their 16 GB RAM Demo
Virtual Machines, it is showing massive lag trying to open folders with
nothing in them. If this doesn't get resolved, all our computers are in 
danger, as they might not load anymore due to insufficient RAM, and if they
do, it will go so slow, you might not be able to access your files, or online
work, each document will not open within 5 minutes due to immense lag. Chrome
may not work, since the system will be using so many resources. My computer is
already having enough difficulty just opening folders, and running certain programs
and it has 8x less available RAM than the machines they are using for the demos.
I can no longer use PhotoShop, which i use for projects, because it doesn't have
enough RAM to use the tools. With all this, our computers have been outdated for
several years, and Microsoft is starting to incrase speed on pushing higher end
computers on us. 4 gigabytes of RAM isn't even considered decent anymore, not even
8 Gigabytes is. So i have set up 3 options to help our workstations, however
they are a bit pricy, each one between $1,900 and $2,800, but it is our only hope
because of how much RAM they have, they will be relevant for a long time, even with
the new update, they will be able to go fast enough to support any program we use
with really good or decent speed. Unfortunately, this is our only option, and since
we will not be able to afford this computer type for everyone, i am willing to share
my laptop with the family, 2-4 hours a day per person, and 100% free-time at 10:00 pm
to 5:30 am for anyone. You are missing out on a good computer, and if we don't hurry,
you can't even make your computer offline to fix it, it will no longer be usable. Our
computers are about to go obsolete. This is a warning for the following devices:
Sean's Laptop
Colleen's Laptop
Vern's Laptop
Chris's laptop
This folder contains 3 available options, choose one before it is too late!